Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 5: Boxes 89-110
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 5: Boxes 89-110
- Box: 90, Folder: 6 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: NEMA Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 242 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    April 15, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Supplement to: NEMA Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 248 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    August 19, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: NEMA Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 243 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Memorandum No. 244 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    April 21, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Memorandum no. 245 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Memorandum No. 246 - Impact of Budgets on People, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    April 28, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Wage and Salary Stabilization - Stock Bonus Trusts and Annuity Plans, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: New Standards for Processing Interplant Petitions, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Wage and Salary Stabilization - Case Processing and Enforcement, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Wage and Salary Stabilization - Petitions for Modification of Vocation Policy, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Wage and Salary Stabilization - Enforcement Procedure, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Status of Exempt Employees under the Fair Labor Standard Act Under Current Interpretations of "On a Salary Basis", Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Federal Regulation of Industrial Safety, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Wage and Salary Stabilization General wage Regulation No. 8 Revised Amendment 3, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: Wage and Salary Stabilization Administrative Explanation of WSB Program Under General Regulation No. 19 - Health and Welfare Plans, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: Wage and Salary Stabilization General Salary Order 12 - New Profit-Sharing and Other Bonuses, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: Wage and Salary Stabilization General Salary Order 12 - New Profit-Sharing and Other Bonuses, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 23: Current Wage Adjustments Reported by U.S. Department of Labor, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 24: Wage and Salary Stabilization - WSB Interpretation Bulletin No. 17, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 25: Wage and Salary Stabilization GWR No. 13, Revised - Amendment 1 Fringe Benefits, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 26: Wage and Salary Stabilization - General Salary Stabilization Regulation No. 8, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 27: Wage and Salary Stabilization - Salary Stabilization Board Interpretations Nos. 6, 7 and 8, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 28: Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 228 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 29: Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 229 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). February 25, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 230 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). February 26, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 231 - Wage and Salary Distribution, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). March 3, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 232 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). March 10, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 265; May 27, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 266; June 9, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 267; June 9, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 268; June 9, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 269; June 10, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 270; June 10, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 271; June 10, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 272; June 18, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum NO. 274; June 18, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 275; June 17, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 276; June 18, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 277; June 23, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 278; July 2, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 279; July 2, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 280; July 3, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 281; July 8, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). July 8, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 282; July 11, 1952`. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 283; July 22, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 284; July 31, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 286; August 5, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 587; August 5, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 288; August 5, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 289; August 13, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 290; August 13, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 291; August 13, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 292; August 18, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 233 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 61: Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 234 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). March 19, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 350 - Date for Complying with Ruling on "While Collar" Pay Deductions Postponed indefinitely, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). December 18, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 235 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 64: Supplement to: NEMA Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 236 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). December 17, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 236 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). March 28, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Industrial Relations Memorandum No. 237 - Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). April 1, 1952. Item is in English.
- Box: 90, Folder: 7 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 293; August 19, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 294; August 19, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 295; August 19, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 296; August 22, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 297; August 26, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 298; November 26, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 298; August 27, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 299; September 2, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 300; September 4, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 301; September 9, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 302; September 8, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 303; September 9, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 304; September 9, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 305; September 16, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 306; September 16, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 307; September 16, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 308; September 26, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 309; September 26, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 310; September 26, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 311; September 26, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 312; September 30, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 313; October 7, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 314; October 9, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 315; October 15, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No.315; October 15, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 316; October 15, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 317; October 22, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 318; October 27, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 319; October 27, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 320; November 6, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 321; November 6, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 322; November 6, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 323; November 6, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 324; November 13, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 325; November 19, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 327; November 19, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 328; November 25, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 329; December 2, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 330; December 17, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 272; December 23, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 331; December 23, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 332; December 23, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 333; January 15, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 340; January 30, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 341; February 9, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 342; February 23, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 343; February 24, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 344; March 12, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 345; April 22, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 346; June 22, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 347; August 10, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 348; August 24, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Industrial Relations Memorandum, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    By NEMA (National Electrical Manufacturers Association). Memorandum No. 349; September 16, 1953. Item is in English.
- Box: 91, Folder: 1 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Instructor's Manual Electricity and its applications to the elevator industry, Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    By Angelo Amatulli. September, 1946. Item is in English.
- Box: 91, Folder: 2 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report on Economic Conditions of the South, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    By The National Emergency Council. June 22, 1938. Item is in English.
- Box: 91, Folder: 3 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Constitution of National Erectors' Association, Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    By National Erectors' Association. Item is in English.
- Box: 91, Folder: 4 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Truth About Subsidies, Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    By The National Farmers Union. Item is in English.
- Box: 91, Folder: 5 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Industry Faces New Crisis, Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    By National Federation of American Shipping. Item is in English.
- Box: 91, Folder: 6 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Personal Newsletter, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    By National Foremen's Institute. November 18, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Supervisor's Personal Newsletter, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    By National Foremen's Institute. November 4, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Supervisor's Personnel Newsletter, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    By National Foremen's Institute. October 21, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Supervisor's Personnel Newsletter, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    By National Foremen's Institute. October 7, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Supervisor's Personnel Newsletter, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    By National Foremen's Institute. September 9, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Supervisor's Personnel Newsletter, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    By National Foremen's Institute. September 23, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Supervisor's Personnel Newsletter, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    By National Foremen's Institute. August 26, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Supervisor's Personnel Newsletter, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    By National Foremen's Institute. August 12, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Supervisor's Personnel Newsletter, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    By National Foremen's Institute. July 29, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Supervisor's Personnel Newsletter, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    By National Foremen's Institute. July 15, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Supervisor's Personnel Newsletter for Staff and Line Management, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    By National Foremen's Institute. July 1, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Supervisor's Personnel Newsletter for Staff and Line Management, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    By National Foremen's Institute. June 17, 1957. Item is in English.